<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>PoshCode</title>
		<link>http://PoshCode.org/video/</link>
		<description>Community resources for PowerShell coders</description>
		<language>en</language>
		<lastbuilddate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 03:35:34 GMT</lastbuilddate>
		<generator>http://HuddledMasses.org/PowerSite</generator>
		<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
			<item>
				<title>AZPosh: PowerShell in a Commercial Application - Tom Towns</title>
				<dc:creator>AZ PowerShell User Group</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/arizona-2018-08-07-azposh-powershell-in-a-commercial-application-tom-towns/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4CsV_mKFh_A"><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/4CsV_mKFh_A/hqdefault.jpg" alt="AZPosh: PowerShell in a Commercial Application - Tom Towns" title="AZPosh: PowerShell in a Commercial Application - Tom Towns" /></a></p>
<p>Presenter(s): Tome Towns
Topic(s): PowerShell in a Commercial Application
In this session Tom will show you how custom modules and functions can be used to validate product requirements, deploy, monitor and support a commercial enterprise class software application.
URL(s):
https://twitter.com/DBDevTom
https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/sql-server/sql-server-editions
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/DevOps
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Continuous_delivery
https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>AZPosh: Thom Schumacher  Parsing SCCM Logs and Taking action on them</title>
				<dc:creator>AZ PowerShell User Group</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/arizona-2018-07-10-azposh-thom-schumacher-parsing-sccm-logs-and-taking-action-on-them/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vSQ3o1TZ1Vc"><img src="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/vSQ3o1TZ1Vc/hqdefault.jpg" alt="AZPosh: Thom Schumacher  Parsing SCCM Logs and Taking action on them" title="AZPosh: Thom Schumacher  Parsing SCCM Logs and Taking action on them" /></a></p>
<p>Presenter(s): Thom Schumacher
Topic(s): Parsing SCCM Logs and Taking action on them
URL(s):
https://azpowershell.wordpress.com/2018/07/03/arizona-powershell-july-10th/
https://github.com/crshnbrn66/SccmUtilities</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>AZPosh: Timothy Warner - Never in Plain Text</title>
				<dc:creator>AZ PowerShell User Group</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/arizona-2018-06-07-azposh-timothy-warner-never-in-plain-text/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZTFFeuGXz6Q"><img src="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/ZTFFeuGXz6Q/hqdefault.jpg" alt="AZPosh: Timothy Warner - Never in Plain Text" title="AZPosh: Timothy Warner - Never in Plain Text" /></a></p>
<p>Topic: Never in Plain Text: Protecting Credentials in PowerShell Scripts
Least-privilege security means two things:</p>
<p>You operate your system as a standard user;
Your scripts generally require different credentials
We never want plain text credentials in our scripts. In this session, Tim performs a survey of the most common (and uncommon) methods to protect credentials in PowerShell source code. We will embrace both community modules as well as Azure Key Vault in our discussion.</p>
<p>We never want plain text credentials in our scripts. In this session, Tim performs a survey of the most common (and uncommon) methods to protect credentials in PowerShell source code. We will embrace both community modules as well as Azure Key Vault in our discussion.</p>
<p>About our Speaker Tim Warner
Timothy Warner is a Microsoft Most Valuable Professional (MVP) in Cloud and Datacenter Management who is based in Nashville, TN. His professional specialties include Microsoft Azure, cross-platform PowerShell, and all things Windows Server-related. You can reach Tim via Twitter (@TechTrainerTim), LinkedIn or his blog.</p>
<p>Tuesday June 5th, from 5:30 pm – 8 pm Arizona Time ( first 30 minutes reserved for speaker setup and for attendees to  network).  Speaker should start around 6 pm.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>AZPosh: Literate DevOps with PowerShell and Jupyter</title>
				<dc:creator>AZ PowerShell User Group</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/arizona-2018-04-03-azposh-literate-devops-with-powershell-and-jupyter/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XssVyyLV9tg"><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/XssVyyLV9tg/hqdefault.jpg" alt="AZPosh: Literate DevOps with PowerShell and Jupyter" title="AZPosh: Literate DevOps with PowerShell and Jupyter" /></a></p>
<p>Presenter(s): <em>Joel “Jaykul” Bennett:</em>
With a brief overview of Donald Knuth’s decades old concept of literate programming, we’ll get an introduction to it’s modern application to DevOps. Learn how you can create programs, deployment scripts, and automation tools with significantly better documentation by changing your attitude toward the construction of programs: concentrate on explaining to human beings what you want the computer to do. We’ll also look at some related tools, like Binder, Jupyter Hubs and Labs, nteract and Hydrogen, with Atom.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>AZPosh: Having fun with PowerShell 6.0</title>
				<dc:creator>AZ PowerShell User Group</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/arizona-2018-03-06-azposh-having-fun-with-powershell-6.0/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zW9arbDttoc"><img src="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/zW9arbDttoc/hqdefault.jpg" alt="AZPosh: Having fun with PowerShell 6.0" title="AZPosh: Having fun with PowerShell 6.0" /></a></p>
<p>Having fun with PowerShell 6.0 – JEA, remoting and cross-
platform
With the recent release of PowerShell 6.0 a lot of questions about remoting, using it across different platforms and what the implications are for JEA. In this session we will briefly go over these core concepts before diving into what PowerShell 6.0 brings to the table and what we are going to pay attention to in the future.
If you are already working with PowerShell 6.0 and you have specific questions be sure to have them prepared, as Yaap will be more than happy to go beyond the content covered in this session.</p>
<p>About our Speaker
Jaap Brasser is a Technical Marketing Engineer at Rubrik and an CDM MVP with a big passion for scripting and automation. As an IT professional Jaap is part of several professional communities, speaks at technical events and writes articles on a variety of subjects on his personal blog and other websites or magazines. As an active member of the PowerShell community he supports users by providing answers in forums, blogs about PowerShell and creates and shares PowerShell modules and functions.
Blog: www.jaapbrasser.com/
Twitter: twitter.com/jaap_brasser
GitHub: github.com/jaapbrasser</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>AZPosh: Infrastructure testing with Pester</title>
				<dc:creator>AZ PowerShell User Group</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/arizona-2018-01-09-azposh-infrastructure-testing-with-pester/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YaslxcopEyU"><img src="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/YaslxcopEyU/hqdefault.jpg" alt="AZPosh: Infrastructure testing with Pester" title="AZPosh: Infrastructure testing with Pester" /></a></p>
<p>During this session we will explore Infrastructure testing with Pester.</p>
<p>About our Speaker:
Adam Bertram is a 20-year veteran of IT. He’s currently an automation engineer, blogger, independent consultant, freelance writer, author, trainer, and presenter. Adam focuses on DevOps, system management, and automation technologies as well as various cloud platforms. He is a Microsoft Cloud and Datacenter Management MVP and efficiency nerd that enjoys teaching others a better way to leverage automation. Catch up on Adam’s articles at http://adamtheautomator.com , Connect on LinkedIn or follow him on Twitter at @adbertram</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>AZPosh: GUI tools using PowerShell</title>
				<dc:creator>AZ PowerShell User Group</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/arizona-2017-12-05-azposh-gui-tools-using-powershell/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ervW7mGQgBY"><img src="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/ervW7mGQgBY/hqdefault.jpg" alt="AZPosh: GUI tools using PowerShell" title="AZPosh: GUI tools using PowerShell" /></a></p>
<p>Presenter(s): During this session we will explore how to create a GUI interface to enhance scripts to become true tools that can be used by non-technical resources.
We will explore using some free tools and some almost free options.
At the conclusion of this session users will have an understanding of form properties and actions and how they relate to PowerShell code.
Attendees are encouraged to bring a thumb drive for sharing of sample code.</p>
<p>One example gui creator for powershell: https://poshgui.com/</p>
<p>Mark MacLachlan is a 25 year IT veteran who specializes in Windows, Active Directory and Microsoft Exchange automation.  He is a former Microsoft employee and VBScript trainer.  Mark embraced PowerShell when it was first released and quickly built on his existing scripting knowledge.  Mark enjoys tool building with PowerShell to make his and his team’s IT duties easier.  His motto is “Work smarter, not harder.”</p>
<p>URL(s): https://poshgui.com/</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>AZPosh:Data Decisions for PowerShell - Jeffery Hicks</title>
				<dc:creator>AZ PowerShell User Group</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/arizona-2017-11-07-azposhdata-decisions-for-powershell-jeffery-hicks/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9BrRtE8XyKQ"><img src="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/9BrRtE8XyKQ/hqdefault.jpg" alt="AZPosh:Data Decisions for PowerShell - Jeffery Hicks" title="AZPosh:Data Decisions for PowerShell - Jeffery Hicks" /></a></p>
<p>Data Decisions for PowerShell</p>
<p>When you create a PowerShell command or tool, sometimes you need to incorporate external data. Perhaps you need to process data from an external source. Or your command needs to commit data to disk in some fashion. Fortunately, there are many options besides a simple text file. Unfortunately, it can be confusing trying to decide what approach to take. In this session, we’ll discuss your options, decision points and a few best practices.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>AZPosh: Automating SSIS, SSRS &amp; SSAS.</title>
				<dc:creator>AZ PowerShell User Group</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/arizona-2017-09-12-azposh-automating-ssis-ssrs-ssas/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uWMW4BNPO4c"><img src="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/uWMW4BNPO4c/hqdefault.jpg" alt="AZPosh: Automating SSIS, SSRS &amp; SSAS." title="AZPosh: Automating SSIS, SSRS &amp; SSAS." /></a></p>
<p>PowerShell has allowed DBAs to manage huge numbers of SQL servers, all
automatically. Now BI practitioners can reap the same benefits of scale and
automation. Scenarios that are normally extremely time consuming can be done
quickly, all with a few lines of PowerShell.
This session will be filled with demos based on real-life scenarios and use-cases.
We will demonstrate how to scale and automate your BI solutions, with a
minimum of effort. In particular, we will be covering PowerShell cmdlets &amp; their
integrations with SSRS, SSIS, &amp; SSAS.
By the end of the session, you’ll be able to accomplish in minutes what would
normally take hours or days. You’ll know ways to quickly deploy hundreds of
SSRS objects to multiple servers; or instantly identify and process stale SSAS
dimensions. Additionally, you will also be able to take care of some pesky ETL
tasks, some by automating SSIS, and others using just plain old PowerShell.</p>
<p>Aaron Nelson is an author, public speaker, blogger, &amp; leader in the community. He has over 15 years of experience in architecture, business intelligence, development, and performance tuning of SQL Server. Aaron has received many certifications and is a six time winner of the Microsoft MVP Award. Aaron leads the PowerShell Virtual Group of PASS ( SQLPS.io ), is a board member of PowerShell.org, and is a volunteer at his local PASS chapter, AtlantaMDF.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>AZPosh: Test Driven Development Using Chef - Robb Scheiefer - Aug 1st 2017</title>
				<dc:creator>AZ PowerShell User Group</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/arizona-2017-08-01-azposh-test-driven-development-using-chef-robb-scheiefer-aug-1st-2017/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2j3vHLDdWRc"><img src="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/2j3vHLDdWRc/hqdefault.jpg" alt="AZPosh: Test Driven Development Using Chef - Robb Scheiefer - Aug 1st 2017" title="AZPosh: Test Driven Development Using Chef - Robb Scheiefer - Aug 1st 2017" /></a></p>
<p>Presenter(s): Robb Scheiefer
Topic(s): Test Driven Development Using Chef
URL(s):
https://twitter.com/chief7
https://azpowershell.wordpress.com/2017/07/21/arizona-powershell-august-1st/
Sponsor: Tek Systems
Description:
Test Driven Development of Chef Infrastructure Automation on Windows Configuration management is currently all the rage in the DevOps space right now but few are investing in the quality of their configuration code like they do with application code. Yet, all the same benefits apply resulting in a faster feedback loop and ultimately cost/time savings. In this session we will cover how to develop Chef cookbooks (with DSC resources) for Windows by writing rspec/Pester tests first. We will review how the red-green-red-green process ensures we have valid and useful tests. For good measure we will also show how mocking works to help isolate your tests. In addition to reviewing existing cookbooks, we will also write some new configuration code in the test-first style during the talk.  Chef, Kitchen, rspec, PowerShell, DSC and Pester make for a power combination when used together to write tests which drive the development of your configuration code. Come hear how we use this stack of tools to write our configuration code at EBSCO with high quality and you can too.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>AZPosh: Getting Started with PowerShell Development in Visual Studio Code</title>
				<dc:creator>AZ PowerShell User Group</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/arizona-2017-06-06-azposh-getting-started-with-powershell-development-in-visual-studio-code/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DxFQ4uf9d7k"><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/DxFQ4uf9d7k/hqdefault.jpg" alt="AZPosh: Getting Started with PowerShell Development in Visual Studio Code" title="AZPosh: Getting Started with PowerShell Development in Visual Studio Code" /></a></p>
<p>Presenter(s): David Wilson
Topic(s): Getting Started with PowerShell Development in Visual Studio Code
URL(s): https://www.eventbrite.com/e/arizona-powershell-users-group-june-tickets-34973684231</p>
<p>Description:
If you’ve written a script in PowerShell then you’ve probably used the PowerShell ISE. Now that PowerShell has gone cross-platform, Visual Studio Code has become the new official editor for PowerShell development. David will show you how to get started using Visual Studio Code for PowerShell development. Learn how you can use Visual Studio Code to develop, debug and test your scripts in Windows or Linux!</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>AZPosh: Mike F. Robbins - PowerShell Non-Monolithic Script Module Design</title>
				<dc:creator>AZ PowerShell User Group</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/arizona-2017-04-04-azposh-mike-f.-robbins-powershell-non-monolithic-script-module-design/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XH7ajz3WT0A"><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/XH7ajz3WT0A/hqdefault.jpg" alt="AZPosh: Mike F. Robbins - PowerShell Non-Monolithic Script Module Design" title="AZPosh: Mike F. Robbins - PowerShell Non-Monolithic Script Module Design" /></a></p>
<p>Time: April 4th, 6PM
Our Speaker: Mike F. Robbins</p>
<p>Topic(s): PowerShell Non-Monolithic Script Module Design
Creating a script module in PowerShell is a very simplistic process, but there are a number of reasons why you might not want to create one huge monolithic PSM1 script module file that contains all of your module’s functions. During this session, Microsoft MVP Mike F Robbins will demonstrate how to separate each of your module’s functions into its own dedicated PS1 file that’s dot-sourced from your script module’s PSM1 file along with discussing this design methodology and the challenges that it creates. Many times resolving one problem seems to create more problems such as cmdlets from other modules showing up as being exported by your module. The solution to these problems and more will be provided during this session. Mike will also demonstrate using a Pester test to validate that all of the functions are indeed exported along with using a function to help automate the module manifest update process when additional functions are added to your module.</p>
<p>URL(s):
mikefrobbins.com</p>
<p>Location:
Tek Systems
2625 South Plaza Drive
Suite #301 : 3rd Floor in the main conference room.
Tempe
AZ</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>AZPosh: Damian Brady - Octopus Deploy for the PowerShell User</title>
				<dc:creator>AZ PowerShell User Group</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/arizona-2017-03-10-azposh-damian-brady-octopus-deploy-for-the-powershell-user/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HXvtW0T67YA"><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/HXvtW0T67YA/hqdefault.jpg" alt="AZPosh: Damian Brady - Octopus Deploy for the PowerShell User" title="AZPosh: Damian Brady - Octopus Deploy for the PowerShell User" /></a></p>
<p>Sound Corrected and Some Info Slides added to the First Minute.</p>
<p>Presenter(s): Damian Brady
Topic(s): Octopus Deploy for the PowerShell User
URL(s):
https://azpowershell.wordpress.com/2017/02/10/arizona-powershell-march/
https://twitter.com/damovisa
https://twitter.com/azpowershell</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>AZPosh: Damian Brady - Octopus Deploy&#160;for the PowerShell User</title>
				<dc:creator>AZ PowerShell User Group</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/arizona-2017-03-07-azposh-damian-brady-octopus-deploy-for-the-powershell-user/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7mQDqpkHCSk"><img src="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/7mQDqpkHCSk/hqdefault.jpg" alt="AZPosh: Damian Brady - Octopus Deploy for the PowerShell User" title="AZPosh: Damian Brady - Octopus Deploy for the PowerShell User" /></a></p>
<p>Presenter(s): Damian Brady
Topic(s): Octopus Deploy for the PowerShell User
URL(s):
https://azpowershell.wordpress.com/2017/02/10/arizona-powershell-march/
https://twitter.com/damovisa
https://twitter.com/azpowershell</p>]]></description>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>