<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>PoshCode</title>
		<link>https://PoshCode.org/video/</link>
		<description>Community resources for PowerShell coders</description>
		<language>en</language>
		<lastbuilddate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 03:35:49 GMT</lastbuilddate>
		<generator>https://HuddledMasses.org/PowerSite</generator>
		<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
			<item>
				<title>PowerShell Web Access - Richard Siddaway - PowerShell Summit 2013</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">https://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2013-2013-05-07-powershell-web-access-richard-siddaway-powershell-summit-2013/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EloMKpvfES8"><img src="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/EloMKpvfES8/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PowerShell Web Access - Richard Siddaway - PowerShell Summit 2013" title="PowerShell Web Access - Richard Siddaway - PowerShell Summit 2013" /></a></p>
<p>PowerShell Web Access is a new feature in Windows Server 2012 that provides a web based PowerShell console. You don't need PowerShell on your client to administer remote machines as long as you have PWA. This session will demonstrate how to configure PWA, its strengths and weaknesses -- you might even see PowerShell being accessed from a non-Windows machine! The security implications of PWA will be discussed. PWA will be compared to other ways to access remote machines through PowerShell including PS Remoting and CIM sessions.</p>
<p>Download companion speaker materials here:
http://powershell.org/wp/2013/04/22/summit-downloads/</p>
<p>Richard Siddaway
Company: Kelway (UK) Ltd
Title: Automation Consultant
Website: http://msmvps.com/blogs/richardsiddaway/default.aspx
Twitter: @RSiddaway
I have been working with Microsoft technologies for over 25 years having spent time in most IT roles including analyst-programmer, server administration, support, DBA and architect. I have been interested in automation techniques (including automating job creation and submission on mainframes many years ago!). I have been using VBScript and WMI since it became available on NT 4. PowerShell caught my interest when I first heard about it and I have been using it since the early beta versions. My blog is mainly about PowerShell. I founded the UK PowerShell user Group in 2007 and I am a PowerShell MVP. I have given numerous talks on PowerShell at various events in the UK, Europe and the USA. I am a frequent speaker for PowerShell user groups worldwide. I have had a number of articles on PowerShell published including expert commentaries on the Microsoft Scripting Games for which I have been a judge for the last three years. I have written two PowerShell books: PowerShell in Practice (Manning 2010) and PowerShell and WMI (Manning 2012) and coauthored PowerShell in Depth (Manning 2013). I am currently writing an introductory book for Active Directory administrators that features PowerShell.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>PoshMon - PowerShell Does Performance Counters - Ed Wilson - PowerShell Summit 2013</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">https://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2013-2013-05-07-poshmon-powershell-does-performance-counters-ed-wilson-powershell-summit-2013/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y8IbadEHoPg"><img src="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/Y8IbadEHoPg/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PoshMon - PowerShell Does Performance Counters - Ed Wilson - PowerShell Summit 2013" title="PoshMon - PowerShell Does Performance Counters - Ed Wilson - PowerShell Summit 2013" /></a></p>
<p>One of the cool features on Windows PowerShell 3.0 is easy consumption of WMI performance counters into Windows PowerShell. In the past, leveraging these performance counters meant writing long lines of cryptic code, calling refresher objects, and dealing with weird timestamp issues. But no more! Using a simple cmdlet, Windows PowerShell throws open the door to the treasure
trove of performance counter information. But where does the oversubscribed IT pro begin? A question on my Windows NT 3.51 MCSE exam stated there are four areas for performance monitoring: disk, memory, network, and CPU. These four resources have not changed much, regardless of the application these basic areas of investigation still ring true. In this session, I talk about discovering performance counters, using performance counters, and storing information gathered from performance counters. The talk will be strengthened by live demos at each stage of the presentation.</p>
<p>Download companion speaker materials here:
http://powershell.org/wp/2013/04/22/summit-downloads/</p>
<p>Ed Wilson
Company: Microsoft Corporation
Title: Microsoft Scripting Guy
Website: http://www.scriptingguys.com
Twitter: @ScriptingGuys
Ed Wilson is the Microsoft Scripting Guy and a well-known scripting expert. He writes the twice daily Hey Scripting Guy! blog (the number 1 blog on TechNet, found at http://blogs.technet.com/b/heyscriptingguy/). He has also spoken at TechEd and at the Microsoft internal TechReady conferences. He is a Microsoft-certified trainer who has delivered a popular Windows PowerShell workshop to Microsoft Premier Customers worldwide. He has written 11 books including 8 on Windows scripting that were published by Microsoft Press. He has also contributed to nearly a dozen other books. He has two Microsoft Press Windows PowerShell 3.0 books: Windows PowerShell 3.0 Step by Step (http://www.amazon.com/Windows-PowerShell-3-0-Step/dp/0735663394/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1360774300&amp;sr=8-1&amp;keywords=powershell+3.0) and Windows PowerShell 3.0 First Steps (http://www.amazon.com/Windows-PowerShell-3-0-First-Steps/dp/0735676151/ref=sr_1_5?ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1360774329&amp;sr=8-5&amp;keywords=powershell+3.0). Ed holds more than 20 industry certifications, including Microsoft Certified Systems Engineer (MCSE) and Certified Information Systems Security Professional (CISSP). Prior to coming to work for Microsoft, he was a senior consultant for a Microsoft Gold Certified Partner where he specialized in Active Directory design and Exchange implementation. In his spare time, he enjoys woodworking, underwater photography, and scuba diving.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Sapien PowerShell Products - David Corrales - PowerShell Summit 2013</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">https://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2013-2013-05-07-sapien-powershell-products-david-corrales-powershell-summit-2013/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3deY6e6Npzo"><img src="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/3deY6e6Npzo/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Sapien PowerShell Products - David Corrales - PowerShell Summit 2013" title="Sapien PowerShell Products - David Corrales - PowerShell Summit 2013" /></a></p>
<p>SAPIEN Technologies will be presenting their PowerShell Studio product during a special lunchtime session.</p>
<p>Download companion speaker materials here:
http://powershell.org/wp/2013/04/22/summit-downloads/</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Standards Based Hardware Management - Steve Lee - PowerShell Summit 2013</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">https://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2013-2013-05-07-standards-based-hardware-management-steve-lee-powershell-summit-2013/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qSE06GkQWV4"><img src="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/qSE06GkQWV4/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Standards Based Hardware Management - Steve Lee - PowerShell Summit 2013" title="Standards Based Hardware Management - Steve Lee - PowerShell Summit 2013" /></a></p>
<p>This session will provide an overview of the CIM standard including Initiatives, Profiles, and Schema. The second part of this session will demonstrate application of CIM and WS-Man using PowerShell to remotely manage Standards-conformant hardware.</p>
<p>Download companion speaker materials here:
http://powershell.org/wp/2013/04/22/summit-downloads/</p>
<p>Steve Lee
Company: Microsoft Corporation
Title: Principal Test Manager
Steve Lee is the Principal Test Manager for the Standards Based Management platform teams within Windows Server. Steve actively represents Microsoft in the Server Desktop Mobile Platforms Working Group and the WS-Management Working Group within the DMTF (Distributed Management Task Force standards body). He is the author of the Physical Computer System View Profile and the Out-of-Band Hardware Management PowerShell Module published on TechNet.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>CIM Sessions - Richard Siddaway - PowerShell Summit 2013</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">https://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2013-2013-05-07-cim-sessions-richard-siddaway-powershell-summit-2013/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KFA-zSojxqw"><img src="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/KFA-zSojxqw/hqdefault.jpg" alt="CIM Sessions - Richard Siddaway - PowerShell Summit 2013" title="CIM Sessions - Richard Siddaway - PowerShell Summit 2013" /></a></p>
<p>The introduction of the CIM cmdlets and &quot;cmdlets over objects&quot; in PowerShell v3 provide new ways to work with WMI. In addition, they bring a new way to access remote systems ? CIM sessions. Analogous to PowerShell remoting sessions they provide a new flexibility when working with WMI and remote machines. This session will demonstrate: How to use CIM sessions against systems running PowerShell v3; How to work with legacy installations of PowerShell v2; How to use the available CIM session options to configure the session to meet your requirements; Compare and contrast working with WMI, CIM and WSMAN cmdlets against remote machines to illustrate the strengths and weaknesses of each; and how to mix and match CIM sessions using WSMAN and DCOM. The key takeaways from this session will be: the CIM cmdlets provide a new way to access WMI; WSMAN is required knowledge; WSMAN and DCOM can both be used with the CIM cmdlets; CIM sessions are easy to use and very powerful; and no more DCOM problems</p>
<p>Download companion speaker materials here:
http://powershell.org/wp/2013/04/22/summit-downloads/</p>
<p>Richard Siddaway
Company: Kelway (UK) Ltd
Title: Automation Consultant
Website: http://msmvps.com/blogs/richardsiddaway/default.aspx
Twitter: @RSiddaway
I have been working with Microsoft technologies for over 25 years having spent time in most IT roles including analyst-programmer, server administration, support, DBA and architect. I have been interested in automation techniques (including automating job creation and submission on mainframes many years ago!). I have been using VBScript and WMI since it became available on NT 4. PowerShell caught my interest when I first heard about it and I have been using it since the early beta versions. My blog is mainly about PowerShell. I founded the UK PowerShell user Group in 2007 and I am a PowerShell MVP. I have given numerous talks on PowerShell at various events in the UK, Europe and the USA. I am a frequent speaker for PowerShell user groups worldwide. I have had a number of articles on PowerShell published including expert commentaries on the Microsoft Scripting Games for which I have been a judge for the last three years. I have written two PowerShell books: PowerShell in Practice (Manning 2010) and PowerShell and WMI (Manning 2012) and coauthored PowerShell in Depth (Manning 2013). I am currently writing an introductory book for Active Directory administrators that features PowerShell.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Configuring Your PowerShell Workflow Environment - Aleksandar Nikolic - PowerShell Summit 2013</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">https://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2013-2013-05-07-configuring-your-powershell-workflow-environment-aleksandar-nikolic-powershell-summit-2013/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1XuB71tLNvg"><img src="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/1XuB71tLNvg/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Configuring Your PowerShell Workflow Environment - Aleksandar Nikolic - PowerShell Summit 2013" title="Configuring Your PowerShell Workflow Environment - Aleksandar Nikolic - PowerShell Summit 2013" /></a></p>
<p>In this session you will learn how to set up your environment to run Windows PowerShell workflows. We will discuss different workflow configurations, how to prepare computers to run workflows, what workflow session configuration is and how to customize it. At the end, you will learn how to properly run your Windows PowerShell workflows.</p>
<p>Download companion speaker materials here:
http://powershell.org/wp/2013/04/22/summit-downloads/</p>
<p>Aleksandar Nikolic
Company: M.O.3.A.K. IT Consulting
Website: http://powershellmagazine.com
Twitter: @alexandair
Aleksandar Nikolic is Microsoft MVP for Windows PowerShell. He is one of the earliest adaptors of Windows PowerShell. Aleksandar is a frequent speaker at the conferences (Microsoft Sinergija, PowerShell Deep Dive, NYC Techstravaganza, KulenDayz) and participates regularly in IT Pro/PowerShell user groups worldwide. He is also a cofounder and editor of the PowerShell Magazine (http://powershellmagazine.com). You can find him on Twitter: https://twitter.com/alexandair.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Creating a Complex and Reusable HTML Reporting Structure - Alan Renouf - PowerShell Summit 2013</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">https://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2013-2013-05-07-creating-a-complex-and-reusable-html-reporting-structure-alan-renouf-powershell-summit-2013/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XsnE_OQGvdo"><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/XsnE_OQGvdo/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Creating a Complex and Reusable HTML Reporting Structure - Alan Renouf - PowerShell Summit 2013" title="Creating a Complex and Reusable HTML Reporting Structure - Alan Renouf - PowerShell Summit 2013" /></a></p>
<p>In this session I will show you the shortcuts and tricks picked up when creating a complex reporting structure with PowerShell, how a simple HTML output script grew to be a reporting structure which can adapt to give detailed, nicely formatted reports on any application or system that has a PowerShell interface, and even some that don't!</p>
<p>Download companion speaker materials here:
http://powershell.org/wp/2013/04/22/summit-downloads/</p>
<p>Alan Renouf
Company: Vmware, Inc.
Title: Senior Technical Marketing Architect
Website: http://virtu-al.net
Twitter: @alanrenouf
Alan Renouf is a Senior Technical Marketing Architect at VMware focused on the automation and integration of VMware products. Alan is a frequent blogger at http://blogs.vmware.com/vipowershell and has a personal blog at http://virtu-al.net. You can follow Alan on twitter as @alanrenouf.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Creating HTML Reports with Style - Jeff Hicks - PowerShell Summit 2013</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">https://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2013-2013-05-07-creating-html-reports-with-style-jeff-hicks-powershell-summit-2013/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pL_Ry5LzX3w"><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/pL_Ry5LzX3w/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Creating HTML Reports with Style - Jeff Hicks - PowerShell Summit 2013" title="Creating HTML Reports with Style - Jeff Hicks - PowerShell Summit 2013" /></a></p>
<p>Creating HTML-based reports in PowerShell on one hand is incredibly easy - pipe a command to ConvertTo-HTML, save to a file and you're done. But the basics leave much to be desired in creating an HTML report that does more than mere present numbers. This session will dive into some techniques for adding flair and pizzazz to your HTML reports.</p>
<p>Download companion speaker materials here:
http://powershell.org/wp/2013/04/22/summit-downloads/</p>
<p>Jeff Hicks
Company: JDH IT Solutions
Title: Independent Author, Trainer and Consultant
URL: http://jdhitsolutions.com/blog
Twitter: @jeffhicks
Jeffery Hicks is a Microsoft MVP in Windows PowerShell, Microsoft Certified Trainer and an IT veteran with over 20 years of experience, much of it spent as an IT consultant specializing in Microsoft server technologies with an emphasis in automation and efficiency. He works today as an independent author, trainer and consultant. Jeff writes the popular Prof. PowerShell column for MPCMag.com, is a regular contributor to the Petri IT Knowledgebase and 4SysOps, and frequent speaker at technology conferences and user groups. If he isn't writing, Jeff is most likely recording training videos for companies like TrainSignal or hanging out in the forums at PowerShell.org. Jeff's latest books are Learn PowerShell 3 in a Month of Lunches, Learn PowerShell Toolmaking in a Month of Lunches and PowerShell in Depth: An Administrators Guide.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Remoting Configuration Deep Dive - Don Jones - PowerShell Summit 2013</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">https://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2013-2013-05-07-remoting-configuration-deep-dive-don-jones-powershell-summit-2013/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-ERyfmOmyoI"><img src="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/-ERyfmOmyoI/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Remoting Configuration Deep Dive - Don Jones - PowerShell Summit 2013" title="Remoting Configuration Deep Dive - Don Jones - PowerShell Summit 2013" /></a></p>
<p>What do you do when Enable-PSRemoting isn't enough? Dig deeper. We'll run through all of the major configuration scenarios, including how to use (and not abuse) TrustedHosts, how to set up an HTTPS listener (and use it), how to do non-domain authentication, how to enable CredSSP and configure it to be less than a major security hole, and more. Pretty much every possible Remoting config, we'll cover. With detailed, step-by-step instructions!</p>
<p>Download companion speaker materials here:
http://powershell.org/wp/2013/04/22/summit-downloads/</p>
<p>Don Jones
Company: Concentrated Technology, LLC
Title: Founder
Website: http://concentratedtech.com
Twitter: @concentrateddon
With more than fifteen years of IT experience, Don Jones is one of the world's leading experts on the Microsoft business technology platform. He's the author of more than 35 books, including Windows PowerShell: TFM, Windows Administrator's Scripting Toolkit, VBScript WMI and ADSI Unleashed, PHP-Nuke Garage, Special Edition Using Commerce Server 2002, Definitive Guide to SQL Server Performance Optimization, and many more. Don is a top-rated and in-demand speaker at conferences such as Microsoft TechEd, Windows Connections, and TechMentor, and is an accomplished IT journalist with features and monthly columns in Microsoft TechNet Magazine, Redmond Magazine, and on Web sites such as TechTarget and MCPMag.com. Don is also a multiple-year recipient of Microsoft's prestigious Most Valuable Professional (MVP) Award, and is the Editor-in-Chief for Realtime Publishers.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Practical PowerShell Integration from Bare Metal to the Cloud - Alan Renouf - PowerShell Summit 2013</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">https://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2013-2013-05-07-practical-powershell-integration-from-bare-metal-to-the-cloud-alan-renouf-powershell-summit-2013/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=msHGx-mxWJA"><img src="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/msHGx-mxWJA/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Practical PowerShell Integration from Bare Metal to the Cloud - Alan Renouf - PowerShell Summit 2013" title="Practical PowerShell Integration from Bare Metal to the Cloud - Alan Renouf - PowerShell Summit 2013" /></a></p>
<p>See how PowerShell can be used as the glue of the datacenter, take information from VMware, Cisco and Microsoft, Glue them all together and go from bare metal up to the cloud and beyond. Learn how PowerShell is now expanding to be the language of choice and how Microsoft and third party products can be tied together to create fantastic solutions.</p>
<p>Download companion speaker materials here:
http://powershell.org/wp/2013/04/22/summit-downloads/</p>
<p>Alan Renouf
Company: Vmware, Inc.
Title: Senior Technical Marketing Architect
Website: http://virtu-al.net
Twitter: @alanrenouf
Alan Renouf is a Senior Technical Marketing Architect at VMware focused on the automation and integration of VMware products. Alan is a frequent blogger at http://blogs.vmware.com/vipowershell and has a personal blog at http://virtu-al.net. You can follow Alan on twitter as @alanrenouf.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Advanced Network Scripting with PowerShell - Lee Holmes - PowerShell Summit 2013</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">https://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2013-2013-05-07-advanced-network-scripting-with-powershell-lee-holmes-powershell-summit-2013/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jMVBN5V0G4Y"><img src="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/jMVBN5V0G4Y/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Advanced Network Scripting with PowerShell - Lee Holmes - PowerShell Summit 2013" title="Advanced Network Scripting with PowerShell - Lee Holmes - PowerShell Summit 2013" /></a></p>
<p>Although PowerShell provides an enormous benefit even when your scripts interact only with the local system, working with data sources from the Internet opens exciting and unique opportunities. Through its cmdlets and access to the networking support in the .NET Framework, PowerShell provides ample opportunities for Internet-enabled administration. In this session, we'll walk through some examples of using PowerShell to get a deeper understanding of the language your computer speaks when it talks to another computer. Along the way, we'll parse and download information from websites, interact with arbitrary TCP streams, and have some fun with network packet captures.</p>
<p>Download companion speaker materials here:
http://powershell.org/wp/2013/04/22/summit-downloads/</p>
<p>Lee Holmes
Company: Microsoft Corporation
Title: Senior Software Development Engineer</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Build Your Demo Environment with Windows PowerShell - Aleksandar Nikolic - PowerShell Summit 2013</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">https://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2013-2013-05-07-build-your-demo-environment-with-windows-powershell-aleksandar-nikolic-powershell-summit-2013/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GXkLtEOM-DM"><img src="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/GXkLtEOM-DM/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Build Your Demo Environment with Windows PowerShell - Aleksandar Nikolic - PowerShell Summit 2013" title="Build Your Demo Environment with Windows PowerShell - Aleksandar Nikolic - PowerShell Summit 2013" /></a></p>
<p>Build Your Demo Environment or a Test Lab with Windows PowerShell</p>
<p>With Windows PowerShell 3.0 and the new Client Hyper-V available in Windows 8, it is so easy, and fun, to automate creation of your demo environment or a test lab infrastructure. You can easily convert ISO files to VHDs, deploy your VMs and configure networking and storage. Join us for this demo-heavy session to see all the steps.</p>
<p>Download companion speaker materials here:
http://powershell.org/wp/2013/04/22/summit-downloads/</p>
<p>Aleksandar Nikolic
Company: M.O.3.A.K. IT Consulting
Website: http://powershellmagazine.com
Twitter: @alexandair
Aleksandar Nikolic is Microsoft MVP for Windows PowerShell. He is one of the earliest adaptors of Windows PowerShell. Aleksandar is a frequent speaker at the conferences (Microsoft Sinergija, PowerShell Deep Dive, NYC Techstravaganza, KulenDayz) and participates regularly in IT Pro/PowerShell user groups worldwide. He is also a cofounder and editor of the PowerShell Magazine (http://powershellmagazine.com). You can find him on Twitter: https://twitter.com/alexandair.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Write Modules, Not Scripts - Ed Wilson - PowerShell Summit 2013</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">https://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2013-2013-05-07-write-modules-not-scripts-ed-wilson-powershell-summit-2013/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U_niW85TtJE"><img src="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/U_niW85TtJE/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Write Modules, Not Scripts - Ed Wilson - PowerShell Summit 2013" title="Write Modules, Not Scripts - Ed Wilson - PowerShell Summit 2013" /></a></p>
<p>Learn how to get the most from Windows PowerShell by learning a simple five-step method to transform your Windows PowerShell code into a highly reusable module. This presentation is a live demo that begins with a single line of Windows PowerShell code, transforms the code into a function, adds comment based help to the function, and converts it into a module. Next, the installation and discovery of Windows PowerShell modules is covered, as is updating the module and creating a Windows PowerShell module manifest.</p>
<p>Download companion speaker materials here:
http://powershell.org/wp/2013/04/22/summit-downloads/</p>
<p>Ed Wilson
Company: Microsoft Corporation
Title: Microsoft Scripting Guy
Website: http://www.scriptingguys.com
Twitter: @ScriptingGuys
Ed Wilson is the Microsoft Scripting Guy and a well-known scripting expert. He writes the twice daily Hey Scripting Guy! blog (the number 1 blog on TechNet, found at http://blogs.technet.com/b/heyscriptingguy/). He has also spoken at TechEd and at the Microsoft internal TechReady conferences. He is a Microsoft-certified trainer who has delivered a popular Windows PowerShell workshop to Microsoft Premier Customers worldwide. He has written 11 books including 8 on Windows scripting that were published by Microsoft Press. He has also contributed to nearly a dozen other books. He has two Microsoft Press Windows PowerShell 3.0 books: Windows PowerShell 3.0 Step by Step (http://www.amazon.com/Windows-PowerShell-3-0-Step/dp/0735663394/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1360774300&amp;sr=8-1&amp;keywords=powershell+3.0) and Windows PowerShell 3.0 First Steps (http://www.amazon.com/Windows-PowerShell-3-0-First-Steps/dp/0735676151/ref=sr_1_5?ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1360774329&amp;sr=8-5&amp;keywords=powershell+3.0). Ed holds more than 20 industry certifications, including Microsoft Certified Systems Engineer (MCSE) and Certified Information Systems Security Professional (CISSP). Prior to coming to work for Microsoft, he was a senior consultant for a Microsoft Gold Certified Partner where he specialized in Active Directory design and Exchange implementation. In his spare time, he enjoys woodworking, underwater photography, and scuba diving.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Device Management With PowerShell - Ricardo Mendes - PowerShell Summit 2013</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">https://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2013-2013-05-07-device-management-with-powershell-ricardo-mendes-powershell-summit-2013/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0NeEU3FHp8I"><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/0NeEU3FHp8I/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Device Management With PowerShell - Ricardo Mendes - PowerShell Summit 2013" title="Device Management With PowerShell - Ricardo Mendes - PowerShell Summit 2013" /></a></p>
<p>This session will explore how Windows PowerShell 3.0 can be used to enumerate, control, and manage hardware components as well as device drivers, similar in capabilities to the Device Manager MMC.</p>
<p>Download companion speaker materials here:
http://powershell.org/wp/2013/04/22/summit-downloads/</p>
<p>Ricardo Mendes
Company: Microsoft Corporation</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>How Secure Can You Be? - Jeff Hicks PowerShell Summit 2013</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">https://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2013-2013-05-07-how-secure-can-you-be-jeff-hicks-powershell-summit-2013/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iV6cYsQDL0Y"><img src="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/iV6cYsQDL0Y/hqdefault.jpg" alt="How Secure Can You Be? - Jeff Hicks PowerShell Summit 2013" title="How Secure Can You Be? - Jeff Hicks PowerShell Summit 2013" /></a></p>
<p>As PowerShell spreads through the enterprise how we handle security and credentials becomes more and more important. There is a trade-off between ease of use and security. But what are you trading? In this session we'll discuss
a number of ways of handling security and credentials as well as some recommended best practices.</p>
<p>Download companion speaker materials here:
http://powershell.org/wp/2013/04/22/summit-downloads/</p>
<p>Jeff Hicks
Company: JDH IT Solutions
Title: Independent Author, Trainer and Consultant
URL: http://jdhitsolutions.com/blog
Twitter: @jeffhicks
Jeffery Hicks is a Microsoft MVP in Windows PowerShell, Microsoft Certified Trainer and an IT veteran with over 20 years of experience, much of it spent as an IT consultant specializing in Microsoft server technologies with an emphasis in automation and efficiency. He works today as an independent author, trainer and consultant. Jeff writes the popular Prof. PowerShell column for MPCMag.com, is a regular contributor to the Petri IT Knowledgebase and 4SysOps, and frequent speaker at technology conferences and user groups. If he isn't writing, Jeff is most likely recording training videos for companies like TrainSignal or hanging out in the forums at PowerShell.org. Jeff's latest books are Learn PowerShell 3 in a Month of Lunches, Learn PowerShell Toolmaking in a Month of Lunches and PowerShell in Depth: An Administrators Guide.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>