<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>PoshCode</title>
		<link>http://PoshCode.org/video/</link>
		<description>Community resources for PowerShell coders</description>
		<language>en</language>
		<lastbuilddate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 07:51:15 GMT</lastbuilddate>
		<generator>http://HuddledMasses.org/PowerSite</generator>
		<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
			<item>
				<title>Advanced Network Scripting with PowerShell - Lee Holmes - PowerShell Summit 2013</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2013-2013-05-07-advanced-network-scripting-with-powershell-lee-holmes-powershell-summit-2013/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jMVBN5V0G4Y"><img src="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/jMVBN5V0G4Y/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Advanced Network Scripting with PowerShell - Lee Holmes - PowerShell Summit 2013" title="Advanced Network Scripting with PowerShell - Lee Holmes - PowerShell Summit 2013" /></a></p>
<p>Although PowerShell provides an enormous benefit even when your scripts interact only with the local system, working with data sources from the Internet opens exciting and unique opportunities. Through its cmdlets and access to the networking support in the .NET Framework, PowerShell provides ample opportunities for Internet-enabled administration. In this session, we'll walk through some examples of using PowerShell to get a deeper understanding of the language your computer speaks when it talks to another computer. Along the way, we'll parse and download information from websites, interact with arbitrary TCP streams, and have some fun with network packet captures.</p>
<p>Download companion speaker materials here:
http://powershell.org/wp/2013/04/22/summit-downloads/</p>
<p>Lee Holmes
Company: Microsoft Corporation
Title: Senior Software Development Engineer</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Build Your Demo Environment with Windows PowerShell - Aleksandar Nikolic - PowerShell Summit 2013</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2013-2013-05-07-build-your-demo-environment-with-windows-powershell-aleksandar-nikolic-powershell-summit-2013/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GXkLtEOM-DM"><img src="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/GXkLtEOM-DM/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Build Your Demo Environment with Windows PowerShell - Aleksandar Nikolic - PowerShell Summit 2013" title="Build Your Demo Environment with Windows PowerShell - Aleksandar Nikolic - PowerShell Summit 2013" /></a></p>
<p>Build Your Demo Environment or a Test Lab with Windows PowerShell</p>
<p>With Windows PowerShell 3.0 and the new Client Hyper-V available in Windows 8, it is so easy, and fun, to automate creation of your demo environment or a test lab infrastructure. You can easily convert ISO files to VHDs, deploy your VMs and configure networking and storage. Join us for this demo-heavy session to see all the steps.</p>
<p>Download companion speaker materials here:
http://powershell.org/wp/2013/04/22/summit-downloads/</p>
<p>Aleksandar Nikolic
Company: M.O.3.A.K. IT Consulting
Website: http://powershellmagazine.com
Twitter: @alexandair
Aleksandar Nikolic is Microsoft MVP for Windows PowerShell. He is one of the earliest adaptors of Windows PowerShell. Aleksandar is a frequent speaker at the conferences (Microsoft Sinergija, PowerShell Deep Dive, NYC Techstravaganza, KulenDayz) and participates regularly in IT Pro/PowerShell user groups worldwide. He is also a cofounder and editor of the PowerShell Magazine (http://powershellmagazine.com). You can find him on Twitter: https://twitter.com/alexandair.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>PoshMon - PowerShell Does Performance Counters - Ed Wilson - PowerShell Summit 2013</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2013-2013-05-07-poshmon-powershell-does-performance-counters-ed-wilson-powershell-summit-2013/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y8IbadEHoPg"><img src="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/Y8IbadEHoPg/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PoshMon - PowerShell Does Performance Counters - Ed Wilson - PowerShell Summit 2013" title="PoshMon - PowerShell Does Performance Counters - Ed Wilson - PowerShell Summit 2013" /></a></p>
<p>One of the cool features on Windows PowerShell 3.0 is easy consumption of WMI performance counters into Windows PowerShell. In the past, leveraging these performance counters meant writing long lines of cryptic code, calling refresher objects, and dealing with weird timestamp issues. But no more! Using a simple cmdlet, Windows PowerShell throws open the door to the treasure
trove of performance counter information. But where does the oversubscribed IT pro begin? A question on my Windows NT 3.51 MCSE exam stated there are four areas for performance monitoring: disk, memory, network, and CPU. These four resources have not changed much, regardless of the application these basic areas of investigation still ring true. In this session, I talk about discovering performance counters, using performance counters, and storing information gathered from performance counters. The talk will be strengthened by live demos at each stage of the presentation.</p>
<p>Download companion speaker materials here:
http://powershell.org/wp/2013/04/22/summit-downloads/</p>
<p>Ed Wilson
Company: Microsoft Corporation
Title: Microsoft Scripting Guy
Website: http://www.scriptingguys.com
Twitter: @ScriptingGuys
Ed Wilson is the Microsoft Scripting Guy and a well-known scripting expert. He writes the twice daily Hey Scripting Guy! blog (the number 1 blog on TechNet, found at http://blogs.technet.com/b/heyscriptingguy/). He has also spoken at TechEd and at the Microsoft internal TechReady conferences. He is a Microsoft-certified trainer who has delivered a popular Windows PowerShell workshop to Microsoft Premier Customers worldwide. He has written 11 books including 8 on Windows scripting that were published by Microsoft Press. He has also contributed to nearly a dozen other books. He has two Microsoft Press Windows PowerShell 3.0 books: Windows PowerShell 3.0 Step by Step (http://www.amazon.com/Windows-PowerShell-3-0-Step/dp/0735663394/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1360774300&amp;sr=8-1&amp;keywords=powershell+3.0) and Windows PowerShell 3.0 First Steps (http://www.amazon.com/Windows-PowerShell-3-0-First-Steps/dp/0735676151/ref=sr_1_5?ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1360774329&amp;sr=8-5&amp;keywords=powershell+3.0). Ed holds more than 20 industry certifications, including Microsoft Certified Systems Engineer (MCSE) and Certified Information Systems Security Professional (CISSP). Prior to coming to work for Microsoft, he was a senior consultant for a Microsoft Gold Certified Partner where he specialized in Active Directory design and Exchange implementation. In his spare time, he enjoys woodworking, underwater photography, and scuba diving.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>PowerShell Web Access - Richard Siddaway - PowerShell Summit 2013</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2013-2013-05-07-powershell-web-access-richard-siddaway-powershell-summit-2013/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EloMKpvfES8"><img src="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/EloMKpvfES8/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PowerShell Web Access - Richard Siddaway - PowerShell Summit 2013" title="PowerShell Web Access - Richard Siddaway - PowerShell Summit 2013" /></a></p>
<p>PowerShell Web Access is a new feature in Windows Server 2012 that provides a web based PowerShell console. You don't need PowerShell on your client to administer remote machines as long as you have PWA. This session will demonstrate how to configure PWA, its strengths and weaknesses -- you might even see PowerShell being accessed from a non-Windows machine! The security implications of PWA will be discussed. PWA will be compared to other ways to access remote machines through PowerShell including PS Remoting and CIM sessions.</p>
<p>Download companion speaker materials here:
http://powershell.org/wp/2013/04/22/summit-downloads/</p>
<p>Richard Siddaway
Company: Kelway (UK) Ltd
Title: Automation Consultant
Website: http://msmvps.com/blogs/richardsiddaway/default.aspx
Twitter: @RSiddaway
I have been working with Microsoft technologies for over 25 years having spent time in most IT roles including analyst-programmer, server administration, support, DBA and architect. I have been interested in automation techniques (including automating job creation and submission on mainframes many years ago!). I have been using VBScript and WMI since it became available on NT 4. PowerShell caught my interest when I first heard about it and I have been using it since the early beta versions. My blog is mainly about PowerShell. I founded the UK PowerShell user Group in 2007 and I am a PowerShell MVP. I have given numerous talks on PowerShell at various events in the UK, Europe and the USA. I am a frequent speaker for PowerShell user groups worldwide. I have had a number of articles on PowerShell published including expert commentaries on the Microsoft Scripting Games for which I have been a judge for the last three years. I have written two PowerShell books: PowerShell in Practice (Manning 2010) and PowerShell and WMI (Manning 2012) and coauthored PowerShell in Depth (Manning 2013). I am currently writing an introductory book for Active Directory administrators that features PowerShell.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Device Management With PowerShell - Ricardo Mendes - PowerShell Summit 2013</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2013-2013-05-07-device-management-with-powershell-ricardo-mendes-powershell-summit-2013/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0NeEU3FHp8I"><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/0NeEU3FHp8I/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Device Management With PowerShell - Ricardo Mendes - PowerShell Summit 2013" title="Device Management With PowerShell - Ricardo Mendes - PowerShell Summit 2013" /></a></p>
<p>This session will explore how Windows PowerShell 3.0 can be used to enumerate, control, and manage hardware components as well as device drivers, similar in capabilities to the Device Manager MMC.</p>
<p>Download companion speaker materials here:
http://powershell.org/wp/2013/04/22/summit-downloads/</p>
<p>Ricardo Mendes
Company: Microsoft Corporation</p>]]></description>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>