<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>PoshCode</title>
		<link>http://PoshCode.org/video/</link>
		<description>Community resources for PowerShell coders</description>
		<language>en</language>
		<lastbuilddate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 22:27:34 GMT</lastbuilddate>
		<generator>http://HuddledMasses.org/PowerSite</generator>
		<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
			<item>
				<title>PhillyPoSH 11/03/2016 - David Wilson - &#39;Creating PowerShell Projects with Plaster&#39;</title>
				<dc:creator>Philly PoSH</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/phillyposh-2016-11-06-phillyposh-11032016-david-wilson-creating-powershell-projects-with-plaster/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0OTLYWSdbtA"><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/0OTLYWSdbtA/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PhillyPoSH 11/03/2016 - David Wilson - 'Creating PowerShell Projects with Plaster'" title="PhillyPoSH 11/03/2016 - David Wilson - 'Creating PowerShell Projects with Plaster'" /></a></p>
<p>David is a software engineer in the PowerShell team at Microsoft, working to evolve the PowerShell development experience. In this presentation David discusses 'Creating PowerShell Projects with Plaster'. Plaster is a new module that makes it easy to create new PowerShell modules and DSC resources using community tools and best practices.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>PhillyPoSH 10/06/2016 - Warren Frame - &#39;Continuous Deployment with PowerShell&#39;</title>
				<dc:creator>Philly PoSH</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/phillyposh-2016-10-12-phillyposh-10062016-warren-frame-continuous-deployment-with-powershell/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jKLf1KjYhTM"><img src="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/jKLf1KjYhTM/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PhillyPoSH 10/06/2016 - Warren Frame - 'Continuous Deployment with PowerShell'" title="PhillyPoSH 10/06/2016 - Warren Frame - 'Continuous Deployment with PowerShell'" /></a></p>
<p>Warren Frame (@pscookiemonster) is an Infrastructure Engineer with a penchant for PowerShell, science, cooking, information security, family, cookies, and the Oxford comma.
For a summary and links to the materials for this meeting please visit : http://phillyposh.org/archive/2016/10/Meeting-Summary.html</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>PhillyPoSH 9/1/2016 - Mike Fal - Exploring SQLPS, the SQL Server Powershell Module&#39;</title>
				<dc:creator>Philly PoSH</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/phillyposh-2016-09-06-phillyposh-912016-mike-fal-exploring-sqlps-the-sql-server-powershell-module/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u0Pexuq1E1I"><img src="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/u0Pexuq1E1I/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PhillyPoSH 9/1/2016 - Mike Fal - Exploring SQLPS, the SQL Server Powershell Module'" title="PhillyPoSH 9/1/2016 - Mike Fal - Exploring SQLPS, the SQL Server Powershell Module'" /></a></p>
<p>Mike Fal (http://www.mikefal.net/) is a specialist in data management technologies. As a community advocate, public speaker, and blogger, Mike is a practicing thought leader for data and automation. He is passionate about DevOps and data, building platforms to optimize, protect, and use data efficiently. Since 1999, Mike has been working in the database field, focusing primarily on SQL Server and specializes in automating data solutions to improve the reliability and efficiency of his environments. He currently works as a SQL Server Consultant for UpSearch, LLC and has been caught playing trombone in public on more than one occasion.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>PhillyPoSH 8/4/2016 - Timothy Warner - Windows PowerShell DSC Implementation Best Practices</title>
				<dc:creator>Philly PoSH</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/phillyposh-2016-08-08-phillyposh-842016-timothy-warner-windows-powershell-dsc-implementation-best-practices/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UPl6SUT2eX0"><img src="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/UPl6SUT2eX0/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PhillyPoSH 8/4/2016 - Timothy Warner - Windows PowerShell DSC Implementation Best Practices" title="PhillyPoSH 8/4/2016 - Timothy Warner - Windows PowerShell DSC Implementation Best Practices" /></a></p>
<p>Timothy Warner is a PowerShell enthusiast, IT pro, tech trainer, and author who is versed in not only Windows but Linux and OSX as well. You can follow him on Twitter (http://timwarnertech.com/index.html) and visit his website (http://timwarnertech.com/index.html) for a list of his training courses, speaking appearances, and books written. You can also check out the courses he teaches at Pluralsite.com.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>PhillyPoSH 5/5/2016 - Steve Parankewich - PowerShell EWS</title>
				<dc:creator>Philly PoSH</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/phillyposh-2016-05-15-phillyposh-552016-steve-parankewich-powershell-ews/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xybG-BBvQ9M"><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/xybG-BBvQ9M/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PhillyPoSH 5/5/2016 - Steve Parankewich - PowerShell EWS" title="PhillyPoSH 5/5/2016 - Steve Parankewich - PowerShell EWS" /></a></p>
<p>Steve Parankewich is a professional Systems Analyst/Engineer/Architect working with Windows, Linux and Novell based services. He is the Author of Powershellblogger.com and the founder of the Boston PowerShell user group. You can find Steve on twitter @powershellblog</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>PhillyPoSH 7/7/2015 - John Mello and TJ Turner</title>
				<dc:creator>Philly PoSH</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/phillyposh-2015-07-08-phillyposh-772015-john-mello-and-tj-turner/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GGr3dQRi5nQ"><img src="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/GGr3dQRi5nQ/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PhillyPoSH 7/7/2015 - John Mello and TJ Turner" title="PhillyPoSH 7/7/2015 - John Mello and TJ Turner" /></a></p>
<p>John Mello gives a presentation on the new ConvertFrom-String cmdlet in the PowerShell V5 preview. Followed by TJ Turner who gives a presentation entitled “What’s in your toolbox?”.</p>
<p>John Mello and TJ Turner are both cofounders of PhillyPosh</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>PhillyPoSH 5/7/2015 - Jim Ficarra - PowerShell and Puppet</title>
				<dc:creator>Philly PoSH</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/phillyposh-2015-05-23-phillyposh-572015-jim-ficarra-powershell-and-puppet/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yBX20V4fSZ8"><img src="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/yBX20V4fSZ8/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PhillyPoSH 5/7/2015 - Jim Ficarra - PowerShell and Puppet" title="PhillyPoSH 5/7/2015 - Jim Ficarra - PowerShell and Puppet" /></a></p>
<p>We had some mic issues but audio picks up at ~2min in.</p>
<p>Puppet is a Configuration Management System framework from PuppetLabs that originated on Linux systems and has been ported to Windows in recent years. While some of the core library of Puppet’s configuration resource types are intended to be cross-platform, there are many extended configuration item requirements specific to Windows that are best solved using native Windows tools. In this presentation, we’ll explore the application of several PowerShell tools, techniques and patterns that help better integrate the power and maturity of Puppet on the Windows Platform.</p>
<p>Jim Ficarra is a Principal Engineer in the Operations Architecture Team for Comcast Cable’s Application Platform Services Group. The team’s responsibilities include application infrastructure design for performance &amp; scalability, automation, and operational excellence.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>PhillyPoSH 3/26/2015 - Steven Murawski : Intermediate DSC – Building DSC Resources</title>
				<dc:creator>Philly PoSH</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/phillyposh-2015-03-30-phillyposh-3262015-steven-murawski-intermediate-dsc-building-dsc-resources/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b8Ekaf0dcb4"><img src="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/b8Ekaf0dcb4/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PhillyPoSH 3/26/2015 - Steven Murawski : Intermediate DSC – Building DSC Resources" title="PhillyPoSH 3/26/2015 - Steven Murawski : Intermediate DSC – Building DSC Resources" /></a></p>
<p>Intermediate DSC – Building DSC Resources
While there are a lot of DSC Resources out in the wild now, you’ll likely still have a need to create a custom resource.  We’ll dive into how we can use our existing PowerShell skills to develop DSC resources.  After that, we’ll touch on some more advanced patterns for ensuring proper operation of our DSC Resources – including testing DSC resources with Pester.</p>
<p>More about Steven:
Steven Murawski is a Community Manager for Chef (the automation platform for the new IT) and a Microsoft MVP in PowerShell.  Steven is a co-host of the Ops All The Things podcast.</p>
<p>Steven also helps run two local user groups, the Greater Milwaukee IT Pro User Community and the Greater Milwaukee Script Club. He speaks regularly to local user groups and can be found at various conferences</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>PhillyPoSH 3/5/2015 - Derek Murawsky : Introducing Chocolatey</title>
				<dc:creator>Philly PoSH</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/phillyposh-2015-03-09-phillyposh-352015-derek-murawsky-introducing-chocolatey/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LqyHyoa_F1c"><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/LqyHyoa_F1c/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PhillyPoSH 3/5/2015 - Derek Murawsky : Introducing Chocolatey" title="PhillyPoSH 3/5/2015 - Derek Murawsky : Introducing Chocolatey" /></a></p>
<p>Chocolatey is a package manager for Windows in the vein of APT and RPM. Written in Powershell and based on Nuget, it allows for easy installation, upgrade, and dependency management of software on Windows. In this talk, I will give an overview of Chocolatey from a Sysadmin point of view, and show how easy it is to create packages of your own.</p>
<p>Derek Murawsky is a IT Professional specializing in system architecture, design, and implementation. He can be found building, cooking, or tinkering with any number of gizmos and gadgets.</p>
<p>You can follow Derek’s blog at www.theendofthetunnel.org</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>PhillyPoSH 1/8/2015 - John Mello : The ForEach and Where methods in Powershell v4</title>
				<dc:creator>Philly PoSH</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/phillyposh-2015-01-13-phillyposh-182015-john-mello-the-foreach-and-where-methods-in-powershell-v4/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vc2Ukz2N9WQ"><img src="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/vc2Ukz2N9WQ/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PhillyPoSH 1/8/2015 - John Mello : The ForEach and Where methods in Powershell v4" title="PhillyPoSH 1/8/2015 - John Mello : The ForEach and Where methods in Powershell v4" /></a></p>
<p>A review of the ForEach and Where methods in Powershell v4 and how they differ from the previous methods</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>PhillyPoSH 10/02/2014 - John Mello : Creating Custom Object, TJ Turner : Run Space Pools</title>
				<dc:creator>Philly PoSH</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/phillyposh-2014-10-13-phillyposh-10022014-john-mello-creating-custom-object-tj-turner-run-space-pools/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H9TIq4ssGzo"><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/H9TIq4ssGzo/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PhillyPoSH 10/02/2014 - John Mello : Creating Custom Object, TJ Turner : Run Space Pools" title="PhillyPoSH 10/02/2014 - John Mello : Creating Custom Object, TJ Turner : Run Space Pools" /></a></p>
<p>John Mello gives a talk on The different custom object creation methods and their performance tradeoffs. Followed by TJ Turner who gives a talk entitled &quot;Intro to basic run space pools.  &quot;</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>PhillyPoSH 09/04/2014 - Jan Egil Ring : Get Started with Windows PowerShell DSC</title>
				<dc:creator>Philly PoSH</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/phillyposh-2014-09-07-phillyposh-09042014-jan-egil-ring-get-started-with-windows-powershell-dsc/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BeStZxknsCM"><img src="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/BeStZxknsCM/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PhillyPoSH 09/04/2014 - Jan Egil Ring : Get Started with Windows PowerShell DSC" title="PhillyPoSH 09/04/2014 - Jan Egil Ring : Get Started with Windows PowerShell DSC" /></a></p>
<p>Jan will explain how to use Windows PowerShell Desired State Configuration (DSC), which was introduced in Windows PowerShell 4.0, to configure your environment. The purpose of DSC is to provide Deployment, Configuration and Compliance capabilities for Windows resources such as a files, services, roles and features, users, groups and anything that can be managed from PowerShell by using custom resources such as a script. During his talk you will. Learn how to use the configuration keyword to define configurations for different resources The two different configuration modes – Pull and Push – and how to configure them. and see several demos on how DSC can be leveraged in the real world
Jan Egil Ring works as a Lead Architect on the Infrastructure Team at Crayon, Norway. He mainly works with Microsoft server-products, and has a strong passion for Windows PowerShell. In addition to being a consultant, he is a Microsoft Certified Trainer. He has obtained several certifications such as MCSE: Server Infrastructure and MCSE: Private Cloud. He has a strong passion for Windows PowerShell, and regularly writes articles for PowerShell Magazine, the Crayon Services blog and the Norwegian TechNet blog. He is also a multiple-year recipient of the Microsoft Most Valuable Professional Award for his contributions in the Windows PowerShell technical community.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>PhillyPoSH 08/07/2014 - Matt Wrock : Boxstarter and More...</title>
				<dc:creator>Philly PoSH</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/phillyposh-2014-08-10-phillyposh-08072014-matt-wrock-boxstarter-and-more/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=olY1g07E8mk"><img src="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/olY1g07E8mk/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PhillyPoSH 08/07/2014 - Matt Wrock : Boxstarter and More..." title="PhillyPoSH 08/07/2014 - Matt Wrock : Boxstarter and More..." /></a></p>
<p>Matt Wrock joins PhillyPoSH to present on deployment automation topics covering Boxstarter, Chocolatey, Vagrant, and automation testing with Chef Test-Kitchen.</p>
<p>Matt will start with some demos of Boxstarter illustrating how it can be used to build a self standing Windows environment with a focus on how to test the package installs on a virtual machine. Then we will explore some other tools and techniques suited for “machine convergence” testing. Many of these tools, like Vagrant and the Chef-based Test-Kitchen, have their roots outside of Windows but can most certainly provide assistance to PowerShell automation.</p>
<p>Matt Wrock has over fifteen years of experience architecting scalable, distributed, high traffic web applications as well as configuration management and deployment automation. Matt currently lives in Woodinville, WA with his wife, two daughters, three dogs, two cats and ridable lawn mower. Until just recently Matt worked for Microsoft as a Sr. Software Engineer and now works for CenturyLink Cloud focusing on data center automation. Matt is project founder of Boxstarter and a committer to Chocolatey and Pester.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>PhillyPoSH 07/03/2014 - Dr. Ferdinand G. Rios : Building PowerShell GUI Tool Solutions</title>
				<dc:creator>Philly PoSH</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/phillyposh-2014-07-05-phillyposh-07032014-dr.-ferdinand-g.-rios-building-powershell-gui-tool-solutions/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1daOFL4lp5E"><img src="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/1daOFL4lp5E/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PhillyPoSH 07/03/2014 - Dr. Ferdinand G. Rios : Building PowerShell GUI Tool Solutions" title="PhillyPoSH 07/03/2014 - Dr. Ferdinand G. Rios : Building PowerShell GUI Tool Solutions" /></a></p>
<p>Ferdinand Rios will discuss the differences between scripts and tools and how to easily create GUI based tools using PowerShell Studio 2014. We're really excited to have Ferdinand with us and to learn all the cool possibilities PowerShell Studio brings to the table. In case you missed it you can also catch Ferdinand and David Corrales from Sapien on a recent episode of the PowerScripting podcast.</p>
<p>Dr. Ferdinand G. Rios is a 25+ year veteran of the software industry. His experience in the field runs the gamut from tech support specialist to developer; from data entry clerk to CEO. Besides his responsibilities as CEO, Dr. Rios enjoys being the lead programmer on SAPIEN's mobile technology application, iPowerShell Pro.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>PhillyPoSH 06/05/2014 - Jeff Hicks : Getting Started with Desired State Configuration (DSC)</title>
				<dc:creator>Philly PoSH</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/phillyposh-2014-06-09-phillyposh-06052014-jeff-hicks-getting-started-with-desired-state-configuration-dsc/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J5ru8h73F0g"><img src="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/J5ru8h73F0g/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PhillyPoSH 06/05/2014 - Jeff Hicks : Getting Started with Desired State Configuration (DSC)" title="PhillyPoSH 06/05/2014 - Jeff Hicks : Getting Started with Desired State Configuration (DSC)" /></a></p>
<p>DSC is the big game changer for IT Pros. With DSC you no longer have to write PowerShell scripts to manage and configure your servers. Now you use PowerShell to build and manage server configurations. Want your server configured a specific way? Build a configuration and the server configures itself! In this presentation we will look at the principals of DSC and explore what it takes to get started using DSC in your environment.
Jeffery Hicks is a multi-year Microsoft MVP in Windows PowerShell, Microsoft Certified Professional and an IT veteran with almost 25 years of experience, much of it spent as an IT infrastructure consultant specializing in Microsoft server technologies with an emphasis in automation and efficiency. He works today as an independent author, trainer and consultant. Jeff writes the popular Prof. PowerShell column for MPCMag.com, is a regular contributor to a variety on online sites, as well as frequent speaker at technology conferences and user groups.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>