<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>PoshCode</title>
		<link>http://PoshCode.org/video/</link>
		<description>Community resources for PowerShell coders</description>
		<language>en</language>
		<lastbuilddate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 20:42:08 GMT</lastbuilddate>
		<generator>http://HuddledMasses.org/PowerSite</generator>
		<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
			<item>
				<title>Omaha PSUG 02/23/2016 - David Jones - PowerShell and Custom Windows Images</title>
				<dc:creator>Omaha PSUG</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/omaha-psug-2016-02-24-omaha-psug-02232016-david-jones-powershell-and-custom-windows-images/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ur1itl0GHaQ"><img src="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/ur1itl0GHaQ/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Omaha PSUG 02/23/2016 - David Jones - PowerShell and Custom Windows Images" title="Omaha PSUG 02/23/2016 - David Jones - PowerShell and Custom Windows Images" /></a></p>
<p>David Jones (@bladefirelight) talks about using PowerShell to create and deploy fully patched Custom WIM Images.  David has spent an extensive amount of time using Desired State Configuration with fully patched  Custom WIM Images converted into VMDK and VHDx files to rapidly deploy servers across his environment and this talk will cover how he is using PowerShell (including a module he built) to rapidly deploy and create this images.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Boe Prox   Tuesday, November 10, 2015 6 06 02 PM</title>
				<dc:creator>Omaha PSUG</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/omaha-psug-2015-11-16-boe-prox-tuesday-november-10-2015-6-06-02-pm/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4w4r1LYcqj4"><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/4w4r1LYcqj4/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Boe Prox   Tuesday, November 10, 2015 6 06 02 PM" title="Boe Prox   Tuesday, November 10, 2015 6 06 02 PM" /></a></p>
<p>Join us this month as Omaha’s own Boe Prox (@proxb) talks about testing your PowerShell code with Pester!  Pester is an open source project on GitHub which provides a framework for running Unit Tests to execute and validate PowerShell commands inside of PowerShell. Pester tests can execute any command or script that is accessible to a pester test file. This can include functions, Cmdlets, Modules and scripts. Pester can be run in ad hoc style in a console or it can be integrated into the Build scripts of a Continuous Integration system.</p>
<p>Boe Prox is a Senior Windows System Administrator and has been using PowerShell since 2008. He is also a recipient of the Microsoft MVP award in Windows PowerShell. He is also a recipient of the Microsoft Community Contributor Award for 2011 and 2012 and is  a moderator on the Hey Scripting Guy forum. He is active both in that forum and in theWindows PowerShell forum as well. He was also a judge for the 2012 &amp; 2013 Scripting Games. His current projects are PoshPAIG , PoshWSUS, PoshEventUI and PoshChat, all available at Codeplex.  He has also published a several articles for Microsoft’s Hey Scripting Guy! blog and the PowerShell Magazine.</p>
<p>Slides for this presentation are available here: http://1drv.ms/1Mj3mWI</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Omaha PSUG 10/27/2015 - Mike Robbins - PowerShell and Desired State Configuration</title>
				<dc:creator>Omaha PSUG</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/omaha-psug-2015-10-28-omaha-psug-10272015-mike-robbins-powershell-and-desired-state-configuration/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Vfth5xUlYLM"><img src="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/Vfth5xUlYLM/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Omaha PSUG 10/27/2015 - Mike Robbins - PowerShell and Desired State Configuration" title="Omaha PSUG 10/27/2015 - Mike Robbins - PowerShell and Desired State Configuration" /></a></p>
<p>PowerShell MVP Mike Robbins joins us live from Mississippi to talk about Using PowerShell Desired State Configuration in your On-Premises Datacenter.</p>
<p>In this day and age, with the virtualization of servers causing systems in your datacenter to multiply faster than a speeding bullet, how do you perform configuration management on all of those systems and the software that they run while operating on a shoestring budget? How do you detect and remediate configuration drift to stay in compliance with your organization’s standards? During this session, PowerShell MVP Mike F Robbins will demonstrate how DSC (Desired State Configuration) can be used to perform configuration management of the systems in your on-premises datacenter to include writing configurations, applying configurations via push and pull mode, and we’ll have a quick discussion about DSC resources. This is a beginner level DSC session, but prior experience with PowerShell is recommended.</p>
<p>Mike F Robbins is a Microsoft MVP on Windows PowerShell and a SAPIEN Technologies MVP. He is a co-author of Windows PowerShell TFM 4th Edition and is a contributing author of a chapter in the PowerShell Deep Dives book. Mike has written guest blog articles for the Hey, Scripting Guy! Blog, PowerShell Magazine, and PowerShell.org. He is the winner of the advanced category in the 2013 PowerShell Scripting Games. Mike is also the leader and co-founder of the Mississippi PowerShell User Group. He blogs at mikefrobbins.com and can be found on twitter @mikefrobbins.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Omaha PSUG 05/26/2015 - John Slack - PowerShell and JEA</title>
				<dc:creator>Omaha PSUG</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/omaha-psug-2015-05-27-omaha-psug-05262015-john-slack-powershell-and-jea/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=erSUlm1juiI"><img src="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/erSUlm1juiI/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Omaha PSUG 05/26/2015 - John Slack - PowerShell and JEA" title="Omaha PSUG 05/26/2015 - John Slack - PowerShell and JEA" /></a></p>
<p>John Slack joins us to talk about the Just Enough Administration (JEA) Toolkit.</p>
<p>What is JEA?  JEA is delivered by using the built-in capabilities of the Windows PowerShell scripting environment and provides standardized methods of constructing an operator experience that can reduce access with a higher level of granularity than was available in traditional access control models.</p>
<p>JEA accomplishes all this by allowing specific users to perform designated administrative tasks on certain servers without giving them administrator rights, and then auditing all actions that these users performed. JEA is based on Windows PowerShell constrained run spaces, a technology that is already being used to secure administrative tasks in environments such as Microsoft Exchange Online.</p>
<p>John Slack is a Program Manager on the PowerShell Team.  He joined the team in 2013 after graduating from Rice University with a BS in Electrical Engineering.  Over the past two years, he has primarily worked on the PowerShell Gallery and Just Enough Administration (JEA)</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Omaha PSUG  03/31/2015 - Trond Hindenes - PowerShell and Service Management Automation</title>
				<dc:creator>Omaha PSUG</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/omaha-psug-2015-04-01-omaha-psug-03312015-trond-hindenes-powershell-and-service-management-automation/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eLKZ0GWAO10"><img src="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/eLKZ0GWAO10/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Omaha PSUG  03/31/2015 - Trond Hindenes - PowerShell and Service Management Automation" title="Omaha PSUG  03/31/2015 - Trond Hindenes - PowerShell and Service Management Automation" /></a></p>
<p>Trond Hindenes speaking to the Omaha PowerShell User Group on PowerShell and Service Management Automation.</p>
<p>Trond Hindenes will be joining us via Lync from the great country of Norway for a presentation on Service Management Automation (SMA).  Trond is a Senior Consultant at Crayon who spends most of his non-snowboarding time working on Microsoft System Center, PowerShell, Active Directory, Virtualization and Microsoft Azure</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Omaha PSUG 11/11/2014 - Matt Graeber - PowerShell and .NET Malware Analysis</title>
				<dc:creator>Omaha PSUG</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/omaha-psug-2014-11-13-omaha-psug-11112014-matt-graeber-powershell-and-.net-malware-analysis/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mPAmVgjt2UE"><img src="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/mPAmVgjt2UE/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Omaha PSUG 11/11/2014 - Matt Graeber - PowerShell and .NET Malware Analysis" title="Omaha PSUG 11/11/2014 - Matt Graeber - PowerShell and .NET Malware Analysis" /></a></p>
<p>Matt Graeber speaking to the Omaha PowerShell User Group on PowerShell and .Net Malware Analysis.</p>
<p>Most people that the extent of &quot;reverse engineering&quot; .NET code is throwing a .NET executable into their decompiler of choice and reading source code. Those people have never had the privilege of analyzing heavily obfuscated code designed to hamper analysis and in some cases, deliberately crash analysis tools. In this talk, Matt will show how he integrates PowerShell into his workflow to overcome most of the challenges that come with analyzing obfuscated .NET code. Get ready for a technical deep dive!</p>
<p>Matt is a malware reverse engineer, security professional, and PowerShell MVP who is always finding new ways to incorporate PowerShell into his workflow. As one of just a handful of security-minded PowerShell hackers, he also promotes PowerShell as an attack platform in an effort to raise awareness of its security implications in the enterprise. Recently, Matt has made extensive use of PowerShell to perform static and dynamic analysis of .NET malware and obfuscation utilities. When he’s not using PowerShell, you will often find him reversing native code in IDA Pro and WinDbg.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Omaha PSUG Initial Meeting</title>
				<dc:creator>Omaha PSUG</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/omaha-psug-2014-07-30-omaha-psug-initial-meeting/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NtAcl64oHH4"><img src="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/NtAcl64oHH4/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Omaha PSUG Initial Meeting" title="Omaha PSUG Initial Meeting" /></a></p>
<p>Don Jones introduction for the initial Omaha PowerShell User Group Meeting</p>]]></description>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>