<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>PoshCode</title>
		<link>http://PoshCode.org/video/</link>
		<description>Community resources for PowerShell coders</description>
		<language>en</language>
		<lastbuilddate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 20:42:09 GMT</lastbuilddate>
		<generator>http://HuddledMasses.org/PowerSite</generator>
		<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
			<item>
				<title>The Seven Secrets of CIM - Brian Wilhite - PowerShell Summit 2014</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2014-2014-05-15-the-seven-secrets-of-cim-brian-wilhite-powershell-summit-2014/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0t_PvMMeJKQ"><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/0t_PvMMeJKQ/hqdefault.jpg" alt="The Seven Secrets of CIM - Brian Wilhite - PowerShell Summit 2014" title="The Seven Secrets of CIM - Brian Wilhite - PowerShell Summit 2014" /></a></p>
<p>Windows PowerShell and WMI are a match made in Redmond... Seriously, these two &quot;Power&quot; houses are spectacular, awe-inspiring, breathtaking and amazing when fused together.  This coming April 28th, Windows PowerShell fiends, myself included, will descend upon the Meydenbauer Center in Bellevue, WA with a mouthwatering appetite for some PowerShell goodness, gluten free.  To satisfy that hardy hunger, come to my session where you'll discover &quot;The Seven Secrets of CIM&quot;.  It's sure to be a PowerShell blast, you will walk away with real world knowledge that you can start practicing immediately.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Using PowerShell as a Reverse Engineering Tool - Matt Graeber - PowerShell Summit 2014</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2014-2014-05-15-using-powershell-as-a-reverse-engineering-tool-matt-graeber-powershell-summit-2014/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=znwFGHmhD_Y"><img src="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/znwFGHmhD_Y/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Using PowerShell as a Reverse Engineering Tool - Matt Graeber - PowerShell Summit 2014" title="Using PowerShell as a Reverse Engineering Tool - Matt Graeber - PowerShell Summit 2014" /></a></p>
<p>Whether you're performing incident response, black box code analysis, or analyzing malicious code, PowerShell is a powerful tool to add to your reverse engineering tool arsenal. In this talk, you will learn how to use PowerShell to analyze binary file formats and reverse engineer managed and unmanaged code. The talk will conclude with an analysis of a real-world malware sample.</p>
<p>(Please note the second half of this great presentation was lost due to a lack of battery power to the laptop)</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Windows System Internals with PowerShell - Adam Driscoll - PowerShell Summit 2014</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2014-2014-05-15-windows-system-internals-with-powershell-adam-driscoll-powershell-summit-2014/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BK7FKEWmyik"><img src="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/BK7FKEWmyik/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Windows System Internals with PowerShell - Adam Driscoll - PowerShell Summit 2014" title="Windows System Internals with PowerShell - Adam Driscoll - PowerShell Summit 2014" /></a></p>
<p>This session will look at the use and implementation of the PoshInternals module. The PoshInternals module exposes a range of functionality for managing Windows systems using internal APIs that are typically not exposed to the end user. We will explore some of the facets of how it was developed and use some of the tools that are currently available.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>WSMan Cmdlets - Richard Siddaway - PowerShell Summit 2014</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2014-2014-05-15-wsman-cmdlets-richard-siddaway-powershell-summit-2014/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=j3IQeWlxJiI"><img src="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/j3IQeWlxJiI/hqdefault.jpg" alt="WSMan Cmdlets - Richard Siddaway - PowerShell Summit 2014" title="WSMan Cmdlets - Richard Siddaway - PowerShell Summit 2014" /></a></p>
<p>PowerShell functionality is becoming increasingly broad. As the breadth of functionality increases there are pockets of useful functionality that get over looked.  The WSMAN cmdlets are one such pocket. You can utilise the WS-Management layer (WSMAN) directly to access a remote machine. They aren't a replacement for PowerShell remoting or CIM sessions but complement both of these technologies and supply an alternative access method. This session will examine how you can use these cmdlets -- where they are useful and where you should use other remote access methods.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Leveraging Web Services with PowerShell - Trond Hindenes - PowerShell Summit 2014</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2014-2014-05-15-leveraging-web-services-with-powershell-trond-hindenes-powershell-summit-2014/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Cl1lLLFT3Mk"><img src="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/Cl1lLLFT3Mk/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Leveraging Web Services with PowerShell - Trond Hindenes - PowerShell Summit 2014" title="Leveraging Web Services with PowerShell - Trond Hindenes - PowerShell Summit 2014" /></a></p>
<p>Web Services are taking over the datacenter. More and more products supply REST apis for developers and admins to tap into. This will be a demo-heavy session covering topics such as: Web Services for the windows admin: What are they? REST, JSON, and why you care. A word on authentication. Demos!</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Leverage Multi-Threading for Speeding Up Your Scripts - Jason Walker - PowerShell Summit 2014</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2014-2014-05-15-leverage-multi-threading-for-speeding-up-your-scripts-jason-walker-powershell-summit-2014/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KtZPUlktLL8"><img src="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/KtZPUlktLL8/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Leverage Multi-Threading for Speeding Up Your Scripts - Jason Walker - PowerShell Summit 2014" title="Leverage Multi-Threading for Speeding Up Your Scripts - Jason Walker - PowerShell Summit 2014" /></a></p>
<p>PowerShell scripts can be slow when running them across your entire environment.  This session we will examine leveraging PowerShell Jobs, PowerShell Remoting, and Runspaces while providing practical examples of each and when you want to use one method over the other. Multi-threading is simpler than you think and an effective way to cut your script execution time down from hours to minutes or even seconds</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>PowerShell for Security Incident Response - Lee Holmes and Joe Bialek - PowerShell Summit 2014</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2014-2014-05-15-powershell-for-security-incident-response-lee-holmes-and-joe-bialek-powershell-summit-2014/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IzDosMnyYIc"><img src="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/IzDosMnyYIc/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PowerShell for Security Incident Response - Lee Holmes and Joe Bialek - PowerShell Summit 2014" title="PowerShell for Security Incident Response - Lee Holmes and Joe Bialek - PowerShell Summit 2014" /></a></p>
<p>Windows PowerShell is becoming increasingly common in all forms of security: administration, operations, and of course security penetration testing and research. This talk will demonstrate how attackers leverage PowerShell for post-exploitation tasks once they break in to a system. We'll show how to help prevent these attacks by following PowerShell's security best practices for both scripting and operational tasks. Buckle your seatbelts!</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>PowerShell Module Design Rules (and When to Bend Them) - Kirk Freiheit - PowerShell Summit 2014</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2014-2014-05-15-powershell-module-design-rules-and-when-to-bend-them-kirk-freiheit-powershell-summit-2014/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xihN15LKvCs"><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/xihN15LKvCs/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PowerShell Module Design Rules (and When to Bend Them) - Kirk Freiheit - PowerShell Summit 2014" title="PowerShell Module Design Rules (and When to Bend Them) - Kirk Freiheit - PowerShell Summit 2014" /></a></p>
<p>Your PowerShell module exposes a detailed contract with your customers -- and goes much deeper than simply using &quot;Verb-Noun&quot; to name your cmdlets.  The rules of effective module design encompass exposed .NET object type design, parameter/property name matching, and other nuances that help you write modules that 'click'.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Advanced PowerShell Eventing Scripting Techniques - Matt Graeber - PowerShell Summit 2014</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2014-2014-05-15-advanced-powershell-eventing-scripting-techniques-matt-graeber-powershell-summit-2014/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2S78sB9OqM4"><img src="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/2S78sB9OqM4/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Advanced PowerShell Eventing Scripting Techniques - Matt Graeber - PowerShell Summit 2014" title="Advanced PowerShell Eventing Scripting Techniques - Matt Graeber - PowerShell Summit 2014" /></a></p>
<p>Those who have needed to deal with eventing and asyncronous IO have probably been disappointed to discover the lack of a full PowerShell scripting environment when writing event handler logic in within a script block. Until this issue is resolved in a future version of PowerShell, workarounds are necessary in order to leverage the full power of PowerShell. This talk will cover techniques for working with objects when dealing with events and asyncronous IO.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>PowerCLI: How to Automate Your VMWare Environment Reports - Matt Griffin - PowerShell Summit 2014</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2014-2014-05-15-powercli-how-to-automate-your-vmware-environment-reports-matt-griffin-powershell-summit-2014/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZQACzw9cEsw"><img src="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/ZQACzw9cEsw/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PowerCLI: How to Automate Your VMWare Environment Reports - Matt Griffin - PowerShell Summit 2014" title="PowerCLI: How to Automate Your VMWare Environment Reports - Matt Griffin - PowerShell Summit 2014" /></a></p>
<p>We are going to cover PowerCLI and PowerCLI for Tenants, focused primarily and handy scripts to audit your own environments with a few simple click clacks of the keyboard. We will explore the cmdlets that VMWare Provides and talk about real world uses of this product.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Parallel Execution with PowerShell - Tome Tanasovski - PowerShell Summit 2014</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2014-2014-05-15-parallel-execution-with-powershell-tome-tanasovski-powershell-summit-2014/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s7CD-hp7Msw"><img src="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/s7CD-hp7Msw/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Parallel Execution with PowerShell - Tome Tanasovski - PowerShell Summit 2014" title="Parallel Execution with PowerShell - Tome Tanasovski - PowerShell Summit 2014" /></a></p>
<p>For the hardcore scripter working in large enterprises or on time-sensitive scripts, it is important to understand what options are available to you in order to take advantage of all of the processing  power on a machine.  We'll explore what is built in to PowerShell, what is native to the .NET language, and a few other techniques that can help you turn your 8-hour script into a 30-minute script</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Cmdlet-ize the Registry - Richard Siddaway - PowerShell Summit 2014</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2014-2014-05-15-cmdlet-ize-the-registry-richard-siddaway-powershell-summit-2014/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xkzAHUndq4w"><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/xkzAHUndq4w/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Cmdlet-ize the Registry - Richard Siddaway - PowerShell Summit 2014" title="Cmdlet-ize the Registry - Richard Siddaway - PowerShell Summit 2014" /></a></p>
<p>PowerShell supplies a number of ways for you to work with the Registry. On the local machine you have the registry provider -- but you can't use it against remote machines. For remote access you can use WMI or .NET. The WMI, CIM and WSMAN cmdlets can be used to work with the registry on remote machines. All of these cmdlets involve using large constants and an awkward syntax with no consistencies between them. This session will show you how to create your own module to work with the registry on the local or remote machines. Using the CDXML -- objects over cmdlets -- technology introduced with PowerShell 3.0 you can take the registry WMI class and make cmdlets to search for , read, write, create and delete items in the registry. Your take away is a module of cmdlets that enable you to work easily with the registry. You will aslo understend the techniques you can use to create your own cmdlets from WMI classes -- this is the way Microsoft writes many of their cmdlets.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Just Enough Admin - Security in a Post-Snowden World - Jeffrey Snover - PowerShell Summit 2014</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2014-2014-05-15-just-enough-admin-security-in-a-post-snowden-world-jeffrey-snover-powershell-summit-2014/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RhXkyBXwE9k"><img src="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/RhXkyBXwE9k/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Just Enough Admin - Security in a Post-Snowden World - Jeffrey Snover - PowerShell Summit 2014" title="Just Enough Admin - Security in a Post-Snowden World - Jeffrey Snover - PowerShell Summit 2014" /></a></p>
<p>When asked what to do about corporate hacking, Ex NSA Director Michael Hayden replied, &quot;Man up and defend yourselves&quot;.   Within a few years, Edward Snowden rocked the world by disclosing information he had gathered using his NSA administrative privileges.  JitJea stands for Just In Time, Just Enough Admin.  It is a PowerShell toolkit that you can use to &quot;man up and defend yourselves&quot; by allowing people to perform admin tasks without giving them admin privileges</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Monitoring Using PowerShell - Josh Swenson - PowerShell Summit 2014</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2014-2014-05-15-monitoring-using-powershell-josh-swenson-powershell-summit-2014/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LJlgHB5QRnc"><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/LJlgHB5QRnc/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Monitoring Using PowerShell - Josh Swenson - PowerShell Summit 2014" title="Monitoring Using PowerShell - Josh Swenson - PowerShell Summit 2014" /></a></p>
<p>Real world examples of how to use PowerShell for monitoring Servers, Websites, Active Directory, Exchange, DNS, DHCP, Anti-virus, WSUS patching, and notification using email and websites. Scripts will be shared.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>On the Job: Putting PowerShell Scheduled Jobs to Work - Jeff Hicks - PowerShell Summit 2014</title>
				<dc:creator>Aaron Hoover</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/powershell-summit-2014-2014-05-15-on-the-job-putting-powershell-scheduled-jobs-to-work-jeff-hicks-powershell-summit-2014/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tsE0b0KFHe8"><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/tsE0b0KFHe8/hqdefault.jpg" alt="On the Job: Putting PowerShell Scheduled Jobs to Work - Jeff Hicks - PowerShell Summit 2014" title="On the Job: Putting PowerShell Scheduled Jobs to Work - Jeff Hicks - PowerShell Summit 2014" /></a></p>
<p>Learn the ins and outs of scheduled jobs in PowerShell. We'll look at some common use cases and managing scheduled jobs across multiple machines. The session will also include a review of changes to scheduled jobs in PowerShell 4.0</p>]]></description>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>