<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>PoshCode</title>
		<link>http://PoshCode.org/video/</link>
		<description>Community resources for PowerShell coders</description>
		<language>en</language>
		<lastbuilddate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 22:27:27 GMT</lastbuilddate>
		<generator>http://HuddledMasses.org/PowerSite</generator>
		<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
			<item>
				<title>PDX PUG Meetup - Michael Lombardi - Docs as UX - 2018-07-11</title>
				<dc:creator>PDX PowerShell User Group</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/pdx-powershell-user-group-2018-07-20-pdx-pug-meetup-michael-lombardi-docs-as-ux-2018-07-11/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8jqwXzBB1iE"><img src="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/8jqwXzBB1iE/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PDX PUG Meetup - Michael Lombardi - Docs as UX - 2018-07-11" title="PDX PUG Meetup - Michael Lombardi - Docs as UX - 2018-07-11" /></a></p>
<p>Find out how you can (and should) treat your documentation as UX. Mike Lombardi will walk you through threefold model of documentation, the many forms of documentation, and tips and advice to help humans produce more and better documentation for their teammates, customers, and future selves. Further, he will demonstrate using the documentarian PowerShell module to scaffold, preview, and build documentation.</p>
<p>Michael Lombardi is a software engineer at Puppet and a contributor to open source projects. He also hosts a tech chat show called chatter ops.
https://chatterops.org/</p>
<p>He also makes time to mentor and teach folks about agile approaches to infrastructure, infrastructure as code, source control, systems thinking, and general engineering. He has open office hours listed here: https://appoint.ly/t/michaeltlombardi</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/barbariankb
Presentation: https://gitpitch.com/michaeltlombardi/documentarian/pdxpres?grs=gitlab#/</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>PDX PUG Meetup - Justin Grote</title>
				<dc:creator>PDX PowerShell User Group</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/pdx-powershell-user-group-2018-06-20-pdx-pug-meetup-justin-grote/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AEUx2r3zH_Q"><img src="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/AEUx2r3zH_Q/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PDX PUG Meetup - Justin Grote" title="PDX PUG Meetup - Justin Grote" /></a></p>
<p>Powershell for Fun and Profit!: Justin Grote will take us through a case study on how his company, Allied Digital Services LLC, leverages Powershell to enhance their managed services infrastructure to drive a revenue-generating IT organization. The overview will start small with &quot;lazy engineering&quot; (fixing/automating repetitive tasks) and work up to fully automated integrations with Powershell modules both on-premise and using Azure Functions/Automation/DSC.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Testing with Juan</title>
				<dc:creator>PDX PowerShell User Group</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/pdx-powershell-user-group-2018-06-15-testing-with-juan/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mqSrGbUIrMI"><img src="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/mqSrGbUIrMI/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Testing with Juan" title="Testing with Juan" /></a></p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>Monthly Meeting - June 20th - Justin Grote - Case Study</title>
				<dc:creator>PDX PowerShell User Group</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/pdx-powershell-user-group-2018-06-07-monthly-meeting-june-20th-justin-grote-case-study/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qgyl-ejmRWA"><img src="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/qgyl-ejmRWA/hqdefault.jpg" alt="Monthly Meeting - June 20th - Justin Grote - Case Study" title="Monthly Meeting - June 20th - Justin Grote - Case Study" /></a></p>
<p>Powershell for Fun and Profit!: Justin Grote will take us through a case study on how his company, Allied Digital Services LLC, leverages Powershell to enhance their managed services infrastructure to drive a revenue-generating IT organization. The overview will start small with &quot;lazy engineering&quot; (fixing/automating repetitive tasks) and work up to fully automated integrations with Powershell modules both on-premise and using Azure Functions/Automation/DSC.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>PDX PUG Meetup - Jordan Smith - PowerShell in the Cloud with Azure Automation</title>
				<dc:creator>PDX PowerShell User Group</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/pdx-powershell-user-group-2018-05-16-pdx-pug-meetup-jordan-smith-powershell-in-the-cloud-with-azure-automation/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IHzqDmbG7W8"><img src="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/IHzqDmbG7W8/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PDX PUG Meetup - Jordan Smith - PowerShell in the Cloud with Azure Automation" title="PDX PUG Meetup - Jordan Smith - PowerShell in the Cloud with Azure Automation" /></a></p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>PDX PUG Meetup - Jordan Smith - PowerShell in the Cloud with Azure Automation</title>
				<dc:creator>PDX PowerShell User Group</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/pdx-powershell-user-group-2018-05-15-pdx-pug-meetup-jordan-smith-powershell-in-the-cloud-with-azure-automation/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BpXXTYf-JKc"><img src="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/BpXXTYf-JKc/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PDX PUG Meetup - Jordan Smith - PowerShell in the Cloud with Azure Automation" title="PDX PUG Meetup - Jordan Smith - PowerShell in the Cloud with Azure Automation" /></a></p>
<p>Jordan Smith will show us how Azure Automation enables an automation execution environment as a service for managing cloud-based and on-premises resources.</p>
<p>Bio:
Jordan Smith - https://twitter.com/jordansmith79
Cloud Solution Architect @Microsoft. #freedom lover #tech #privacy #powershell #msft #azure</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>PDX PUG Meetup   Eric Courville 2018-03-14</title>
				<dc:creator>PDX PowerShell User Group</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/pdx-powershell-user-group-2018-03-20-pdx-pug-meetup-eric-courville-2018-03-14/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7Rmz8eD9Zas"><img src="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/7Rmz8eD9Zas/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PDX PUG Meetup   Eric Courville 2018-03-14" title="PDX PUG Meetup   Eric Courville 2018-03-14" /></a></p>
<p>Eric Courville - Managing AWS with the AWS Tools for PowerShell</p>
<p>Summary:
Amazon Web Services is the market leader in the Cloud with dozens of services. AWS can be difficult to manage via the web console at scale luckily AWS provides many SDK's and cli tools to help you with your automation. In this talk we'll review the best practices for connecting PowerShell to AWS via IAM Keys, and Roles. We will also check out some use cases for generating reports on your environment as well as interacting with services such as S3, EC2, and more.</p>
<p>Bio:
Eric Courville With over 20 years of IT experience Eric Courville has managed a wide variety of Enterprise Applications ranging from E-commerce to Enterprise Resource Planning. For the last decade he has concentrated primarily on cloud technologies in Azure, and AWS. As a former Microsoft MVP in Cloud and Datacenter and the Founder of the NorCal PowerShell User Group Eric has advocated PowerShell's benefits to Microsoft professionals.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>PDX PUG Meetup   Brandon Olin 2018-02-28</title>
				<dc:creator>PDX PowerShell User Group</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/pdx-powershell-user-group-2018-03-20-pdx-pug-meetup-brandon-olin-2018-02-28/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=APDJcIqFZZk"><img src="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/APDJcIqFZZk/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PDX PUG Meetup   Brandon Olin 2018-02-28" title="PDX PUG Meetup   Brandon Olin 2018-02-28" /></a></p>
<p>Brandon Olin - PowerShell Classes: Here be Dragons</p>
<p>Summary:
Classes are a powerful capability in PowerShell and are meant to provide a familiar development experience to more traditional programmers. You will not experience calm skies and quiet seas though. This talk will show you where the dragons lurk and help you navigate the stormy seas.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
			<item>
				<title>PUG Meetup   Steve Murawski 2018-01-22</title>
				<dc:creator>PDX PowerShell User Group</dc:creator>
				<guid ispermalink="true">http://PoshCode.org/video/pdx-powershell-user-group-2018-03-18-pug-meetup-steve-murawski-2018-01-22/index.html</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SaihBTz1Qd4"><img src="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/SaihBTz1Qd4/hqdefault.jpg" alt="PUG Meetup   Steve Murawski 2018-01-22" title="PUG Meetup   Steve Murawski 2018-01-22" /></a></p>
<p>Steven Murawski is a Developer Advocate at Microsoft. He's had years of experience helping organization go faster.</p>
<p>In this meetup Steven Murawski talks about continuous deployment.</p>
<p>Twitter: @StevenMurawski - https://twitter.com/StevenMurawski
Or you can use the twitter hashtag #LoECDA (Leage of Extraodinary Cloud Developer Advocates, link below) to reach Steven and his team on twitter.</p>
<p>https://twitter.com/search?q=%23LoECDA&amp;src=tyah</p>
<p>Title:
Slow is Smooth
Smooth is fast</p>
<p>Abstract:
Looking for a place to get started with some DevOps practices? Already trying some tooling and not seeing the return you expected? Then, my friend, it’s time we had a chat about pipelines. Now, CI/CD (continuous integration/continuous delivery) pipelines aren’t necessarily the first thing operations teams look for when attempting to tackle a problem or implement a solution. And I’ve heard many of the arguments – with the chief of those being, “I’m not some startup. We don’t deploy changes tens or hundreds of times a day. We deploy every 4 months and we like it (or at least that’s what we have to like contractually).” While that may be true, my guess that your environment changes a bit more than that and the changes that happen outside those well-defined maintenance windows is what ends up causing most of our pain. Adding a pipeline to control the delivery of change forces us to slow down and think about the types of changes we make and how to automate and validate them. Once we’ve done that, making these changes becomes easier and easier. My firearms instructor from the police science program (years ago) had a saying which captures this, “Slow is Smooth, and Smooth is Fast”. By making our change process smooth, we put ourselves in a place where we can consistently deliver change on demand. CI/CD is about speed and readiness, not only about volume. Join me for a chat about why building a pipeline for infrastructure changes, especially in slow environments, is both possible and extremely rewarding. We’ll also look at some tooling to help make standing up those pipelines easy enough that we can try it over a lunch break.</p>]]></description>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>